Two heads are better than one.
Heads of State is a action, thriller, comedy film directed by Ilya Naishuller.
The UK Prime Minister and US President have a public
rivalry that risks their countries' alliance.
But when they become targets of a powerful enemy, they're forced to rely
on each other as they go on a wild, multinational run.
Allied with Noel, a brilliant MI6 agent, they must find a way to
thwart a conspiracy that threatens the free world.
Will Derringer, played by John Cena.
Sam Clarke, played by Idris Elba.
Noel Bisset, played by Priyanka Chopra Jonas.
Viktor Gradov, played by Paddy Considine.
VP Elizabeth Kirk, played by Carla Gugino.
Arthur Hammond, played by Stephen Root.
Heads of State is a 2025 action comedy film directed by Ilya Naishuller.
It stars Idris Elba as the British Prime Minister and John Cena as the President of the United States, two
world leaders who are forced to work together after becoming targets of a foreign adversary.
The supporting cast includes Priyanka Chopra, Jack Quaid,
Paddy Considine, Stephen Root, and Carla Gugino.
The film was released worldwide on 2 July 2025 by
Amazon MGM Studios via Prime Video.
The film explores themes of usa president, head of state, mi6,
british prime minister, duringcreditsstinger.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.